<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Harish Guda</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Harish Guda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Information on Creating Websites with R</title>
      <link>/post/2019/04/18/website-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/04/18/website-info/</guid>
      <description>I have always wanted to build attractive websites and still have a lot of control on the various facets of the website. I had previously owned a Google Site, which I never liked. I am not a professional with regards to web-development. Besides, my needs were minimal. With little knowledge on this topic, I did what everyone else does – dive straight into it.
I am quite comfortable with R, and when Yihui Xie and co-authors came out with the book on blogdown, I decided to try it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Om Vighnaraja</title>
      <link>/post/2019/04/01/om-vighnaraja-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/04/01/om-vighnaraja-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello all!
This is my first post on my new website/blog, thus the title Om Vighnaraja (instead of a Hello World). My hope is to keep y’all updated with content regularly.
Thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi.
I am Harish Guda. I am an Assistant Professor in the Department of Supply Chain Management at the W.P. Carey School of Business at Arizona State University.
My research interests are at the interface of technology, marketplace design and operations/supply chain management.
I am an avid R enthusiast.
Contact  Email: hguda [AT] asu [DOT] edu. Office: BA 427. Mail: Business Administration, 300 E Lemon St., Tempe, AZ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Interests In my research, I study incentive and information design problems to solve operational problems that arise in large marketplaces.
Areas of applications include the emerging on-demand economy, agriculture (in developing economies) and omnichannel retail.
Working Papers  &amp;ldquo;Seemingly-Beneficial&amp;rdquo; Interventions.
 Joint work with Milind Dawande and Ganesh Janakirmanan. PDF, SSRN.  The Economics of Agricultural Support Prices in Developing Economies.
 Joint work with Tharanga Rajapakshe, Milind Dawande and Ganesh Janakiraman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Arizona State University University of Texas at Dallas  OPRE 3310:  Spring 2017: 4.95&amp;frasl;5. Fall 2017: 4.84&amp;frasl;5.   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>