<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Harish Guda</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Harish Guda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Information on Creating Websites with R</title>
      <link>/post/2019/04/18/website-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/04/18/website-info/</guid>
      <description>Update: Much of this information is available in detail at multiple places, including:
The Little Dataset,Official Blogdown E-Book,Alison Hill (who is a co-author on the textbook),among others.
I had previously owned a Google Site, which I never liked. I am quite comfortable with R, and when Yihui Xie and co-authors came out with the book on blogdown, I decided to try it. However, it can be still quite difficult with no experience to HTML, or prior exposure to CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Om Vighnaraja</title>
      <link>/post/2019/04/01/om-vighnaraja-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2019/04/01/om-vighnaraja-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello all!
This is my first post on my new website/blog, thus the title Om Vighnaraja (instead of a Hello World). My hope is to keep y’all updated with content regularly.
One of my favorite things about RMD files is that it compiles math so beautifully. For example,
Fix \(d, w \in [0, 1]\). The indifferent agent \(\hat{\theta} \in [0, 1]\) can be obtained by the following equation:\[w\Bigg(\frac{d}{F(\hat{\theta})}\Bigg) - \hat{\theta} = 0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi.
I am Harish Guda. I am an Assistant Professor in the Department of Supply Chain Management at the W.P. Carey School of Business at Arizona State University.
My research interests are at the interface of technology, marketplace design and operations/supply chain management.
I am an avid R enthusiast.
Contact  Email: hguda [AT] asu [DOT] edu. Office: BA 427, 300 E Lemon St., Tempe, AZ. 85287 Phone: 480 - 727 - 3561.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code</title>
      <link>/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/code/</guid>
      <description> This webpage:
 Github Repo. Post.   My Github repos.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Interests I study incentive and information design problems that arise in large platforms/marketplaces.
Areas of applications include the gig- and sharing-economy, agriculture (in developing economies) and omnichannel retail.
Working Papers  &amp;ldquo;Seemingly-Beneficial&amp;rdquo; Interventions.  Joint work with Milind Dawande and Ganesh Janakirmanan. PDF, SSRN.  The Economics of Agricultural Support Prices in Developing Economies.  Joint work with Tharanga Rajapakshe, Milind Dawande and Ganesh Janakiraman. SSRN.   Publications  Your Uber is Arriving: Managing On-Demand Workers through Sure Pricing, Forecast Communication and Worker Incentives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Arizona State University  SCM 551: Operations Planning and Execution - MBA Elective.
 SCM 502: Operations and Supply Chain Management - MBA Core.
  University of Texas at Dallas  OPRE 3310: Introduction to Operations Management - BS (BA) Core.  Syllabus Spring 2017: 4.95&amp;frasl;5. Fall 2017: 4.84&amp;frasl;5.   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>