<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Harish Guda</title>
    <link>https://harishguda.me/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Harish Guda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://harishguda.me/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Max-Min Inequality</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2023/03/31/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2023/03/31/research/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite results in optimization is the max-min inequality. This is taught in just about every introductory course in optimization, math. for econ, and/or allied courses. The result is as follows.
The ResultConsider a bivariate function \(f(z, w)\), \(z \in Z\), \(w \in W\). It’s easier to think of the sets \(Z\) and \(W\) as finite sets, or a convex subset of \(\mathbb{R}\) (although the result is more general).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expected Mean Residual Lifetime at the Time of Failure</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2022/12/24/expected-mean-residual-lifetime-at-the-time-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2022/12/24/expected-mean-residual-lifetime-at-the-time-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>In a recent paper I worked on, I defined an interesting notion for a random variable called the expected mean residual life at the time of failure. I had not seen this quantity discussed in the prior literature. So, I decided to pen some ideas below.
Mean Residual Lifetime and Hazard RateConsider a random variable, say \(X\), that is drawn from a p.d.f. \(f(\cdot)\) and c.d.f \(F(\cdot)\). The mean residual life of \(X\) at \(t\) is defined as:\[MRL_X(t) = \mathbb{E}[X-t | X &amp;gt; t].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beamer Template for W.P. Carey Affiliated Researchers</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2021/05/12/research-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2021/05/12/research-resources/</guid>
      <description>(Disclaimer: This is my own creation. Users can use this at their own discretion)
A Simple Beamer TemplateI created a simple Beamer template based on a research presentation I gave at a recent conference. I realized there was nothing specific to my department/school available out in the internet, so I had to create one from scratch.
Here are the sample slides: PDF
Please feel free to fork this from my Github repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision Making Under Costly Search</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2021/03/18/teaching-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2021/03/18/teaching-resources/</guid>
      <description>Choice Models 101Choice models – the theory that studies how individual decision makers (e.g., consumers) make decisions when faced with a collection of alternatives – is of interest to several research disciplines. The canonical choice model is as follows.
A single decision-maker chooses one among a collection \(N\) alternatives, indexed by \(i \in [N]\).1 His (consumption) utility from consuming alternative \(i\) is:\[U_i = v_i + \epsilon_i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Templates for First-Time Instructors</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2019/12/18/teaching-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2019/12/18/teaching-resources/</guid>
      <description>I am writing this post as I complete my first quarter of teaching as an Assistant Professor. I taught the core Operations and Supply Chain Management to FT MBAs.1
As I went through this process for the first time, I realized that I needed templates for various files (e.g., syllabus, exams, homework assignments, case writeups, instruction slides, etc.). While there was an abundance of such resources online, it is hard for a single user to try out everything to weed out the bad ones from the good ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Information on Creating Websites with R</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2019/04/18/website-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2019/04/18/website-info/</guid>
      <description>Update: Much of this information is available in detail at multiple places, including:
The Little Dataset,Official Blogdown E-Book,Alison Hill (who is a co-author on the textbook),among others.
I had previously owned a Google Site, which I never liked. I am quite comfortable with R, and when Yihui Xie and co-authors came out with the book on blogdown, I decided to try it. However, it can be still quite difficult with no experience to HTML, or prior exposure to CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Om Vighnaraja</title>
      <link>https://harishguda.me/post/2019/04/01/om-vighnaraja-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://harishguda.me/post/2019/04/01/om-vighnaraja-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello all!
This is my first post on my new website/blog, thus the title Om Vighnaraja (instead of a Hello World). My hope is to keep y’all updated with content regularly.
One of my favorite things about RMD files is that it compiles math so beautifully. For example,
Fix \(d, w \in [0, 1]\). The indifferent agent \(\hat{\theta} \in [0, 1]\) can be obtained by the following equation:\[w\Bigg(\frac{d}{F(\hat{\theta})}\Bigg) - \hat{\theta} = 0.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
